https://www.mining-journal.com/static/terms-conditions

share
Aspermont Media Limited (Aspermont Media, we, us, our) is a print, web and tablet edition publisher to the natural resources and related industry sectors.
Subscription to or use of any Aspermont Media product is subject to the following terms and conditions (Standard Terms and Conditions):
Content Terms & Conditions
Mining Journal content (including any information we publish regarding Third Party Products) is only for your general information and entertainment purposes and is not intended to address your particular requirements.
In particular, Mining Journal content, including user-generated content and any other content provided by third parties and distributed by mining-journal.com, does not constitute any form of advice, recommendation, representation, endorsement or arrangement by Mining Journal or Aspermont.
It is not intended to be and should not be relied upon by users in making (or refraining from making) any specific investment, purchase, sale or other decisions. Appropriate independent advice should be obtained before making any such decision, such as from a qualified financial adviser.
Any agreements, transactions or other arrangements made between you and any third party named on (or linked to from) mining-journal.com are at your own responsibility and entered into at your own risk. Any information that you receive via mining-jorunal.com, whether or not it is classified as "real-time", may have stopped being current by the time it reaches you. Share price information may be rounded up/down and therefore may not be entirely accurate.
Commodities pricing data is provided by Quandl and represents end or day or delayed pricing benchmarks. The data published is for information purposes only and follows Quandl's terms and conditions. Data is sourced from the Chicago Board of Trade, Intercontinental Board of Trade, London Metal Exchange (end of day prices) and Chicago Mercantile Exchange.
Aspermont and its employees make no representation as to the quality, accuracy or completeness of data or that the use of such data or information will not infringe any patent, intellectual property or proprietary rights of any party.
Data published does constitute advice and Aspermont's shall not be liable for any claim, loss, harm, illness or other damage or injury arising from access to or use of data or information.
General Terms & Conditions
By subscribing to an Aspermont Media product you have entered a contract (Subscription Contract) with Aspermont Media. The term of the Subscription Contract is for the period (Subscription Period) nominated by you on the subscription form, registration form, tablet registration page or iTunes purchase page.
Subscription prices quoted by Aspermont Media are inclusive of delivery costs for the print element, where applicable.
Subject to the provisions of the Data Protection Act 1988, by entering the Subscription Contract you agree that the personal information provided by you may be used by Aspermont Media to provide the service you have requested and you:
Consent to Aspermont Media's use of your personal information in accordance with Aspermont Media's Privacy Policy;
Acknowledge that the Standard Terms and Conditions and Privacy Policy may be modified by Aspermont Media from time to time;
Acknowledge that it is your responsibility to regularly review the Standard Terms and Conditions and Privacy Policy; and
Agree to any modification made by Aspermont Media to the Standard Terms and Conditions and Privacy Policy.
Website Terms & Conditions
A standard subscription to any Aspermont Media website product entitles the subscription account holder to access the standard news and content on the newsletter(s) and website(s).
Website user licenses and login details for Aspermont Media Ltd products are for use only by the individual(s) specified by you and are not to be shared or used to provide access to multiple users on a network.
iPad Edition Terms & Conditions
When purchasing from the Apple App Store, A ‘1 Year (iPad-only)' subscription costs £399.99, and an ‘Individual issue' costs £35.
Issues will be downloadable on each Friday that falls within your subscription period.
Your iTunes account will be charged when you choose to purchase a subscription.
At the end of the twelve month subscription period your subscription will renew unless you choose to cancel.
Your iTunes account will be charged the renewal cost for the product you purchased within 24 hours of the end of your current subscriptions period.
You may manage your subscription or cancel the auto renewal of your subscription at any time via your iTunes Account settings.
iPad edition subscription sales are final. If you choose to cancel, your subscription will cease at the end of the current period. No refunds will be given.
Print Terms & Conditions
You must ensure Aspermont Media is provided with the correct contact and delivery information and order details on subscription order forms or registration forms. Aspermont Media will not be liable for any consequences flowing from such errors or incorrect information including, but not limited to, failure to receive Aspermont Media Publications to the correct address. You must notify Aspermont Media of any changes to this or any other relevant information in writing to subscriptions@aspermontmedia.com.
You may cancel your subscription to a print Aspermont Media product at any time during the Subscription Period by advising Aspermont Media of the cancellation in writing to subscriptions@aspermontmedia.com.
Aspermont Media will not, under any circumstances, provide a refund for copies of Aspermont Media Publications sent to the delivery address specified by you
Cancellation Policies
Print and Digital subscriptions purchased through our website or our subscription team:
Aspermont will not, under any circumstances, provide a refund for Aspermont Publications received by you.
Please read below if you are a new customer who has taken one of our introductory offers:
1 Month trial (Renews automatically each month) - If you have taken a 1 month trial for £1 you can cancel your subscription at any time and we will stop payment from the next payable date. If you do not cancel your subscription, we will continue to take payment each month at the digital monthly trial rate of £132. To cancel your subscription you will need to inform us at least 10 days before your next payment is due to be taken.
12 month subscription (1 year contract, 1 upfront payment) - Your subscription is paid in one instalment for a minimum term of 12 months. At the end of your subscription, we will notify you that we will renew your order automatically. If you do not wish to continue your subscription you will need to inform us at least 20 days in advance of your expiry date.
iPad or iPhone Edition subscriptions purchased through the Apple App Store:
Subscription sales are final. If you choose to cancel, your subscription will cease at the end of the current period. No refunds will be given.
You may manage your subscription or cancel the auto renewal of your subscription at any time via your iTunes Account settings.
For any questions regarding these terms and conditions or your subscription, please email our team at subscriptions@aspermontmedia.com.
Most read articles
1
Petra makes $40M from blue diamond sale
Precious stones
2
Scrap metal use destined to disappoint: Woodmac
Bulks
3
Copyright © 2000-2020
Aspermont Media Ltd. All rights reserved. Aspermont Media is a company registered in England and Wales. Company No. 08096447. VAT No. 136738101. Aspermont Media, WeWork, 1 Poultry, London, England, EC2R 8EJ.
Select site
Login
